Okay, now to continue the previous loom,
what you're going to do after, after you check out
the pivots and what the topics of them are,
what you're going to do is go to Drawing.
Hit Google Drive, click on Master File,
click on KyleM, and then search
for Mason Littlejohn.
and then go into the to Mason Content,
2026,
go to the most recent batch,
I think it is October Week 1,
right? Then what you're going to do is
make a copy, right?
Make a copy. Very important.
Rename it as the date for this.
This is October Week 2 Topics.
This is going to be October Week 2 Long Form Match.
But instead of duplicating it inside this folder,
what you're going to do is Copy it to my computer.
Once that
is all set and done,
rename this. For this,
keep it empty for now.
Keep it empty. And then what you're going to do is delete
all of this. Right?
Delete all of this. Clear formatting.
And then, you take the topic sheet here.
Add to new split view, and open the Google Docs as
well. And what you're going to do here is,
you need to take a look at the perspective here.
This is the perspective.
And then what you're going to do is, just write in here,
Operator, in his 30s,
calling out what he sees people in their
60s and 70s get wrong.
Unapologetic,
but never a jab at anyone
he knows personally.
This is The Vehicle The Longform
Vehicle. Longform.
After this, do the same for every topic.
Do the same for every topic,
okay? After you let us say that it
is all said and done, let's just say,
for example, it's all said and What you're going to do
is bold it.
Bold. Then space it out like that.
Space it out. Now,
let us assume that you got this correctly.
What you're going to do is start.
Okay. So it should appear on my start.
Okay. Do you understand?